It has begun. Nightly Title Dialogue Series
This is Sora Akane of Uka. And,
Yes. I'm Yurie Fujii from Namaari Talk.
I'm Yurie Fujii from Namaari Talk.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yay!
Yes, I'm Yurie Fujii of Namaari Talk. So, this is the first time I've met you,
It's kind of an unusual, but not unusual, combination.
Here is the thumbnail. Here is the thumbnail.
Yay!
I collaborated with Miyu once before,
I had collaborated with Miyu once before,
It's been a while since we collaborated.
We haven't had any live performances together recently,
So it feels like it's been a long time.
Yay!
I just got some sweets and was eating them earlier.
You ate it? That was fast.
I gave her a piece of candy with a note saying, "Lucky you.
I'm a good girl.
Yay!
Then what should I call you?
I usually call you Miyu-chan,
What do you call me?
Sora-chan?
I don't think I call you by your name.
That's true.
What do you like?
Do you like Lucky?
You want Lucky? You want lucky?
Because I want it to penetrate.
You want Lucky to penetrate?
Not Miyu, not Fujitani, but Lucky.
Lucky, not Fujitani.
Why?
Because it sounds like a dog.
Lucky likes dogs.
I don't like dogs, but I like doggy-like Lucky.
It's going to sound strange, but for a while, I wanted to have a thicker face,
The foreign face? I wanted to be beautiful,
There was a time when I wanted people to call me Lucky,
I wanted to be called Lucky.
I wanted to be called Lucky,
I think I'll call you Lucky instead of Lucky.
I'm talking about something that doesn't matter.
What do you call it? What should we call him?
Let's go with the first name that comes to mind.
Sky.
We'll be bringing you Lucky and Sky today.
Please do.
We're going to play a game to get to know each other better.
Our specialty?
I'm good at it.
I'm not so good at it, so I'm going to try my best.
So, our first game will be a nighttime and idle gesture game.
Let's see...
Yes, I see. I see.
I would like to explain the rules.
It seems that there is a subject in this nighttime-kun, It's like there's a subject in this nighttime-kun,
It's in there.
The person in charge of gestures draws two themes,
The person in charge of gestures draws two themes, and then does a gesture that combines the two themes.
For example, if you see two words, "nighttime idols," the person in charge of gestures will make a gesture combining the two words,
The person in charge of answering the questions is supposed to express the nighttime and the idol with gestures.
The person in charge of answering the questions must guess what the two subjects are.
The goal is to get as many correct answers as possible in two minutes.
Who goes first?
If I win, I'll draw first.
OK.
First, I'll draw with a goo.
If you win, you draw first.
I'll give you a question first.
You give me a question, and I'll answer it.
I'll answer.
Next announcement
All right, let's get started!
Oh no. There are so many.
Two. Lucky me.
Tell me if you see one.
Can I tell you about this?
It's open.
Did you see two?
I saw two.
Can I go now?
Yes, I'm ready.
Okay.
What? What?
Hey! Lucky!
What? What do you mean?
No!
I don't know!
It's hard!
Oh, come on! You see Lucky? These two are Lucky's 10 chances.
Lucky shows it again.
I showed him.
All right, let's go!
Have you seen two?
Not yet.
Yes, I have. Have you seen them? You already hid them.
Maybe.
Yes, I did. I hid it.
Oh, I wonder if you can see it when you stand up.
Okay, I'll do it like this.
What should I do?
Fireworks?
Whoo.
Whew. Whew.
Train? Train?
No.
Shinkansen?
Whew.
Is it haunted? A ghost?
Whew. Whew.
Which way?
Oh, I just made a mistake.
What?
Uh, bus?
Train?
Hyuto,
Shinkansen?
Airplane?
Something like that.
Pass, pass, pass. Next. Next.
Next.
And then..,
Pull. Pull.
It's hard.
What is it? Pull.
Here we go.
Fuyo.
Wrap?
Woo.
Rap battle?
To.
Ew.
Singing?
Uh-oh.
Recording?
That's great.
Two or one?Two or one?
One? Okay, one. Next.
Okay.
We don't have time for this.
Let's see, let's see.
Eh, difficult.
Okay.
Okay?
Let's see.
Laugh?
Uh...
It's difficult.
Waku-chou?
And... I'm done with it.
That's enough.
To... To...
Congratulations.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday?
Birthday.
Birthday cake.
Ah.
Ew.
Bye.
No.
Gal? Gal?
No.No, it's not.
Woo.
Did you see that?
What's the first one?
What's this?
This is an amusement park.
It's more like...
It's an amusement park and...
This is a roller coaster.
And this is a Ferris wheel.
You can only see it when you're on the Ferris wheel.
It's like you're looking at it from underneath the Ferris wheel.
And the rest?
An amusement park and a horror movie.
A movie.
And the second one?
Two more things. A rap battle and a recording session.
Oh, yeah, that's a good one.
The third one was a time break when I was really funny.
It was really hard to be funny.
It was really hard to be really funny.
It was difficult.
I got one right!
Warning for the next episode
The crying spirit was so moved...
Wow!
Next time, next time.
Keep your eyes closed.
Yes, ma'am.Yes, sir.
This is...
It's good, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Very good.
Is it good?
Yes, okay, okay.
Okay. - Okay.
He's running. He's running. He's coming by the school.
Okay, this is just a rap battle for now.
How's that? How's it going? How's it going? This is what I'm talking about. Let's see, Mine Train, Whee!
No, no, no. Skydiving. Bus.
Harder. Next, next, next.
I'm not done yet. Oh, man, I could eat each and every one of these.
I can eat each and every one of these.
Sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi!
Sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi, sushi!
Shabu-shabu... You're crazy!
Ten.
Next
This is hard!
Wait a minute.
Yay!
Group photo
Nice picture
That way
This is hard
This skill is also strong
I'm going to have to go through a huge, huge rub to pull off a difficult 8-dance IV.I'm a huge dork and I'm buying a difficult 8-dance IV.
I don't remember waving my arms around.
I'm sure it's in there.
You did it, Carbis?
You know what makes me think hag18 Kingdom.
At least the first one is.
Yes, sir.
It's a birthday cake and...
How did I do that?
It's something like this, right?
It's like a movie that makes you cry.
It's a good movie.
I'm glad you liked it.
That's great.
That was great.
He's good, he's an expressive person.
And Majikel is amazing.
Majiwinkel did it.
I did it, so Majiwinkel was amazing.
You can't go to the barbecue.
Freedom.
Freedom was scared.
The other thing that was hard was this.
Photography and...
Loneliness.
I didn't know what loneliness was, so I passed.
It's a little difficult.It's a little difficult to take a picture of this.
It's hard to take a picture of this!
It's difficult!
It's a little bit difficult
And this is
Marathon!
It was a marathon.
I said running.
That was close.
It was close.
And a horror movie.
You danced, you danced, you danced well.
Nut Battle
I got three.
That was great.
Thank you very much.
So, that's it.
It was a game of night and idle gestures.
How was it? Try it.
It was great.
You know, Skye...
I've learned that you're a very expressive person.
I'm going to ask
I'm going to tell the members
"Skye was an expressive person.
I'd like to make it hard to say that.
It's embarrassing. Please don't do it.